<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<mib definition="SNA-LLC-MIB">
    <imports>
        <mibImport>
            <sourceMib>SNMPv2-SMI-v1</sourceMib>
            <import>experimental</import>
            <import>Counter32</import>
            <import>Integer32</import>
            <import>TimeTicks</import>
        </mibImport>
        <mibImport>
            <sourceMib>RFC-1212</sourceMib>
            <import>OBJECT-TYPE</import>
        </mibImport>
        <mibImport>
            <sourceMib>RFC-1215</sourceMib>
            <import>TRAP-TYPE</import>
        </mibImport>
        <mibImport>
            <sourceMib>SNMPv2-TC-v1</sourceMib>
            <import>DisplayString</import>
            <import>RowStatus</import>
        </mibImport>
        <mibImport>
            <sourceMib>RFC1213-MIB</sourceMib>
            <import>ifIndex</import>
        </mibImport>
    </imports>
    <objects>
        <mibObject>
            <objectIdentifier>
                <objectName>snaDLCexp</objectName>
                <objectId>51</objectId>
                <parent>experimental</parent>
            </objectIdentifier>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectIdentifier>
                <objectName>llc</objectName>
                <objectId>1</objectId>
                <parent>snaDLCexp</parent>
            </objectIdentifier>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectIdentifier>
                <objectName>llcPortGroup</objectName>
                <objectId>1</objectId>
                <parent>llc</parent>
            </objectIdentifier>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectIdentifier>
                <objectName>llcSapGroup</objectName>
                <objectId>2</objectId>
                <parent>llc</parent>
            </objectIdentifier>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectIdentifier>
                <objectName>llcCcGroup</objectName>
                <objectId>3</objectId>
                <parent>llc</parent>
            </objectIdentifier>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectIdentifier>
                <objectName>llcTraps</objectName>
                <objectId>4</objectId>
                <parent>llc</parent>
            </objectIdentifier>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectIdentifier>
                <objectName>llcConformance</objectName>
                <objectId>5</objectId>
                <parent>llc</parent>
            </objectIdentifier>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectIdentifier>
                <objectName>llcCompliances</objectName>
                <objectId>1</objectId>
                <parent>llcConformance</parent>
            </objectIdentifier>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectIdentifier>
                <objectName>llcGroups</objectName>
                <objectId>2</objectId>
                <parent>llcConformance</parent>
            </objectIdentifier>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectIdentifier>
                <objectName>llcCoreGroups</objectName>
                <objectId>1</objectId>
                <parent>llcGroups</parent>
            </objectIdentifier>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcPortAdminTable</objectName>
                <objectId>1</objectId>
                <parent>llcPortGroup</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <sequence>LlcPortAdminEntry</sequence>
                </syntax>
                <access>not-accessible</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This table contains objects that can be&lt;br&gt;changed to manage an LLC port.    Changing one&lt;br&gt;of these parameters may take effect in the&lt;br&gt;operating port immediately or may wait until&lt;br&gt;the interface is restarted depending on the&lt;br&gt;details of the implementation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most of the objects in this read-write table&lt;br&gt;have corresponding read-only objects in the&lt;br&gt;llcPortOperTable that return the current&lt;br&gt;operating value.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The operating values may be different from&lt;br&gt;these configured values if  a configured&lt;br&gt;parameter was changed after the interface was&lt;br&gt;started.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcPortAdminEntry</objectName>
                <objectId>1</objectId>
                <parent>llcPortAdminTable</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>LlcPortAdminEntry</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>not-accessible</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>A list of configured values for an LLC port.</description>
                <indices>
                    <index>ifIndex</index>
                </indices>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcPortAdminName</objectName>
                <objectId>1</objectId>
                <parent>llcPortAdminEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>DisplayString(SIZE(1..10))</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-write</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>An octet string that defines the physical port&lt;br&gt;to which this interface is assigned.  It has&lt;br&gt;implementation-specific significance. Its value&lt;br&gt;shall be unique within the administered&lt;br&gt;system.  It must contain only ASCII printable&lt;br&gt;characters.  Should an implementation choose to&lt;br&gt;accept a write operation  for this object, it&lt;br&gt;causes the logical port definition associated&lt;br&gt;with the table instance to be moved to  a&lt;br&gt;different physical port.  A write operation&lt;br&gt;shall not take effect until the port is cycled&lt;br&gt;inactive.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcPortAdminState</objectName>
                <objectId>2</objectId>
                <parent>llcPortAdminEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>INTEGER</type>
                    <valueList>
                        <valueItem>
                            <label>disabled</label>
                            <val>1</val>
                        </valueItem>
                        <valueItem>
                            <label>enabled</label>
                            <val>2</val>
                        </valueItem>
                    </valueList>
                    <defaultValue>enabled</defaultValue>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-write</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This parameter controls the desired state of&lt;br&gt;the LLC protocol for this interface.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcPortAdminMaxIPDUOctetsSend</objectName>
                <objectId>3</objectId>
                <parent>llcPortAdminEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>Integer32</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-write</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object denotes the default maximum I PDU&lt;br&gt;size, in octets, that LLCs on this port may&lt;br&gt;send to their remote LLC partners. This count&lt;br&gt;is referred to as 'N1' in the IEEE 802.2&lt;br&gt;specification [??].&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This port default value may be overridden by a&lt;br&gt;non-zero SAP default value in the&lt;br&gt;llcSapAdminMaxIPDUOctetsSend  object or by a&lt;br&gt;non-zero value in the&lt;br&gt;llcCcAdminMaxIPDUOctetsSend object.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;At connection setup, the remote LLC may send,&lt;br&gt;using an XID frame, the maximum I PDU size&lt;br&gt;which it is prepared to receive. If so, an&lt;br&gt;implementation may choose to override the&lt;br&gt;administered maximum PDU size with the&lt;br&gt;dynamically learned value and should reflect&lt;br&gt;this in the llcCcOperMaxIPDUOctetsSend object&lt;br&gt;for the connection component.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The I PDU size includes all octets in a frame,&lt;br&gt;excluding framing characters, the MAC header&lt;br&gt;and link link header.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcPortAdminMaxIPDUOctetsRcv</objectName>
                <objectId>4</objectId>
                <parent>llcPortAdminEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>Integer32</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-write</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object denotes the default maximum I PDU size,&lt;br&gt;in octets, that LLCs on this port can expect to receive&lt;br&gt;from their remote LLC partners. This count is referred&lt;br&gt;to as 'N1' in the IEEE 802.2 specification [??]&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This port default value may be overridden by a&lt;br&gt;non-zero SAP default value in the&lt;br&gt;llcSapAdminMaxIPDUOctetsRcv object or by a non-zero&lt;br&gt;value in the llcCcAdminMaxIPDUOctetsRcvd object.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;At connection setup, an implementation may choose to&lt;br&gt;send this value to the remote LLC, using an XID&lt;br&gt;frame.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The I PDU size includes all octets in a frame with the&lt;br&gt;exception of the framing characters, the MAC header&lt;br&gt;and the link header.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcPortAdminMaxUnackedIPDUsSend</objectName>
                <objectId>5</objectId>
                <parent>llcPortAdminEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>INTEGER(1..127)</type>
                    <defaultValue>1</defaultValue>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-write</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object denotes the default maximum&lt;br&gt;consequetive unacknowledged I PDU frames that&lt;br&gt;LLCs on this port may send to their remote LLC&lt;br&gt;partners. This count is referred to as 'k' in&lt;br&gt;the IEEE 802.2 specification [??].&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This port default value may be overridden by a&lt;br&gt;non-zero SAP default value in the&lt;br&gt;llcSapAdminMaxUnackedIPDUsSend  object or by a&lt;br&gt;non-zero value in the&lt;br&gt;llcCcAdminMaxUnackedIPDUsSend object.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;At connection setup, the remote LLC may send,&lt;br&gt;using an XID frame, the maximum number of&lt;br&gt;unacknowledged I PDUs which it is prepared to&lt;br&gt;receive. If so, an implementation may choose to&lt;br&gt;override the administered maximum number of&lt;br&gt;unacknowledged PDUs with the dynamicly learned&lt;br&gt;value and should reflect this in the&lt;br&gt;llcCcOperMaxUnackedIPDUsSend object for the&lt;br&gt;connection component.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcPortAdminMaxUnackedIPDUsRcv</objectName>
                <objectId>6</objectId>
                <parent>llcPortAdminEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>INTEGER(1..127)</type>
                    <defaultValue>1</defaultValue>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-write</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object denotes the default maximum number&lt;br&gt;of unacknowledged I PDUs that LLCs on this port&lt;br&gt;can expect to receive from their remote LLC&lt;br&gt;partners. This count is referred to as 'k' in&lt;br&gt;the IEEE 802.2 specification [??].&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This port default value may be overridden by a&lt;br&gt;non-zero SAP default value in the&lt;br&gt;llcSapAdminMaxUnackedIPDUsRcv object or by a&lt;br&gt;non-zero value in the&lt;br&gt;llcCcAdminMaxUnackedIPDUsRcvd object.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;At connection setup, an implementation may&lt;br&gt;choose to send this value to the remote LLC,&lt;br&gt;using an XID frame.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcPortAdminMaxRetransmits</objectName>
                <objectId>7</objectId>
                <parent>llcPortAdminEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>INTEGER</type>
                    <defaultValue>2</defaultValue>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-write</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object denotes the default value for the&lt;br&gt;maximum number of times which LLCs on this port&lt;br&gt;shall retry a PDU following the expiration of&lt;br&gt;the acknowledgement timer, the P-bit timer or&lt;br&gt;the reject timer. When these retries are&lt;br&gt;exhausted, the link shall be declared inactive.&lt;br&gt;This count is referred to as 'N2' in the IEEE&lt;br&gt;802.2 specification [??].&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This port default value may be overridden by a&lt;br&gt;non-zero SAP default value in the&lt;br&gt;llcSapAdminMaxretransmits object or by a&lt;br&gt;non-zero value in the llcCcAdminMaxRetransmits&lt;br&gt;object.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcPortAdminAckTimer</objectName>
                <objectId>8</objectId>
                <parent>llcPortAdminEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>TimeTicks</type>
                    <defaultValue>1</defaultValue>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-write</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object denotes the default value for the&lt;br&gt;time interval during which the LLCs on this port&lt;br&gt;shall expect to receive either:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1) an acknowledgement to one or more outstanding&lt;br&gt;I PDUs.  or 2) a response PDU to an unnumbered&lt;br&gt;command PDU.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The expiration of this timer shall cause the&lt;br&gt;frame unacknowledged frames to be retransmitted&lt;br&gt;(up to N2 times).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;alue in the&lt;br&gt;llcSapAdminAckTimer object or by a non-zero&lt;br&gt;value in the llcCcAdminAckTimer object.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcPortAdminPbitTimer</objectName>
                <objectId>9</objectId>
                <parent>llcPortAdminEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>TimeTicks</type>
                    <defaultValue>1</defaultValue>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-write</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object denotes the default value for the&lt;br&gt;time interval during which the LLCs on this&lt;br&gt;port shall expect to receive a PDU with the F&lt;br&gt;bit set to '1' in response to a Type 2 command&lt;br&gt;with the P bit set to '1'.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The expiration of this timer shall cause the&lt;br&gt;command with the poll bit to be retransmitted&lt;br&gt;(up to N2 times).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This port default value may be overridden by a&lt;br&gt;non-zero SAP default value in the&lt;br&gt;llcSapAdminPbitTimer object or by a non-zero&lt;br&gt;value in the llcCcAdminPbitTimer object.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcPortAdminRejTimer</objectName>
                <objectId>10</objectId>
                <parent>llcPortAdminEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>TimeTicks</type>
                    <defaultValue>1</defaultValue>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-write</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object denotes the default value for the&lt;br&gt;time interval during which the LLCs on this&lt;br&gt;port shall expect to receive a reply to a REJ&lt;br&gt;PDU.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The expiration of this timer shall cause the&lt;br&gt;REJ PDU to be retransmitted (up to N2 times).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This port default value may be overridden by a&lt;br&gt;non-zero SAP default value in the&lt;br&gt;llcSapAdminRejTimer object or by a non-zero&lt;br&gt;value in the llcCcAdminRejTimer object.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcPortAdminBusyTimer</objectName>
                <objectId>11</objectId>
                <parent>llcPortAdminEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>TimeTicks</type>
                    <defaultValue>1</defaultValue>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-write</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object denotes the default value for the&lt;br&gt;time interval during which the LLCs on this&lt;br&gt;port shall expect to receive an indication that&lt;br&gt;a busy condition at the remote LLC has&lt;br&gt;cleared.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The expiration of this timer shall cause the&lt;br&gt;link to be declared inactive.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This port default value may be overridden by a&lt;br&gt;non-zero SAP default value in the&lt;br&gt;llcSapAdminBusyTimer object or by a non-zero&lt;br&gt;value in the llcCcAdminBusyTimer object.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcPortAdminInactTimer</objectName>
                <objectId>12</objectId>
                <parent>llcPortAdminEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>TimeTicks</type>
                    <defaultValue>1</defaultValue>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-write</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object denotes the default value for the&lt;br&gt;time interval during which the LLCs on this&lt;br&gt;port shall expect to receive any PDU from the&lt;br&gt;remote LLC.  This function is not described in&lt;br&gt;the IEEE 802.2 specification [??] but is widely&lt;br&gt;implemented.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The expiration of this timer shall cause the&lt;br&gt;local LLC to send a PDU to the remote LLC with&lt;br&gt;the P bit set to '1'.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This port default value may be overridden by a&lt;br&gt;non-zero SAP default value in the&lt;br&gt;llcSapAdminInactTimer object or by a non-zero&lt;br&gt;value in the llcCcAdminInactTimer object.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Any value for this object less than or equal to&lt;br&gt;the acknowledgement timer shall mean that the&lt;br&gt;timer is not used.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcPortAdminDelayAckCount</objectName>
                <objectId>13</objectId>
                <parent>llcPortAdminEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>INTEGER</type>
                    <defaultValue>1</defaultValue>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-write</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object denotes the default value for the&lt;br&gt;maximum number of consequetive I PDUs which the&lt;br&gt;LLCs on this port shall receive during the&lt;br&gt;interval defined by llcCcOperDelayTimertime&lt;br&gt;without sending an immediate acknowledgement.&lt;br&gt;This must be less than or equal to the value of&lt;br&gt;llcCcOperMaxUnackIPDURcv. This function is not&lt;br&gt;described in the IEEE 802.2 specification [??]&lt;br&gt;but is widely implemented.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This port default value may be overridden by a&lt;br&gt;non-zero SAP default value in the&lt;br&gt;llcSapAdminDelayAckCount object or by a&lt;br&gt;non-zero value in the llcCcAdminDelayCount&lt;br&gt;object.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A value of one indicates that acknowledgments&lt;br&gt;will be sent immediately and that the value of&lt;br&gt;llcPortAdminDelayAckTimer shall be ignored.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcPortAdminDelayAckTimer</objectName>
                <objectId>14</objectId>
                <parent>llcPortAdminEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>TimeTicks</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-write</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object denotes the default value for the&lt;br&gt;time interval during which the LLCs on this&lt;br&gt;port shall delay acknowledgment of one or more&lt;br&gt;I PDUs (up to the value of&lt;br&gt;llcCcOperDelayAckCount). This function is not&lt;br&gt;described in the IEEE 802.2 specification [??]&lt;br&gt;but is widely implemented.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The expiration of this timer shall cause the&lt;br&gt;local LLC to acknowledge all unacknowledged I&lt;br&gt;PDUs.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This object is associated with the&lt;br&gt;llcSapAdminDelayAckCount object and is only&lt;br&gt;defined if that object has a value greater than&lt;br&gt;one.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcPortAdminSimRim</objectName>
                <objectId>15</objectId>
                <parent>llcPortAdminEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>INTEGER</type>
                    <valueList>
                        <valueItem>
                            <label>no</label>
                            <val>1</val>
                        </valueItem>
                        <valueItem>
                            <label>yes</label>
                            <val>2</val>
                        </valueItem>
                    </valueList>
                    <defaultValue>no</defaultValue>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-write</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object controls the support for&lt;br&gt;transmission and receipt of SIM and RIM control&lt;br&gt;frames for this port.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcPortOperTable</objectName>
                <objectId>2</objectId>
                <parent>llcPortGroup</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <sequence>LlcPortOperEntry</sequence>
                </syntax>
                <access>not-accessible</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This table contains current LLC port&lt;br&gt;parameters.  Many of these objects have&lt;br&gt;corresponding objects inthe llcPortAdminTable.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcPortOperEntry</objectName>
                <objectId>1</objectId>
                <parent>llcPortOperTable</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>LlcPortOperEntry</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>not-accessible</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>Currently set parameters for a specific LLC port.</description>
                <indices>
                    <index>ifIndex</index>
                </indices>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcPortOperName</objectName>
                <objectId>1</objectId>
                <parent>llcPortOperEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>DisplayString(SIZE(1..8))</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-only</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>An octet string that describes the physical&lt;br&gt;port to which this interface is currently&lt;br&gt;attached.  It has  implementation-specific&lt;br&gt;significance.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcPortOperISTATUS</objectName>
                <objectId>2</objectId>
                <parent>llcPortOperEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>INTEGER</type>
                    <valueList>
                        <valueItem>
                            <label>inactive</label>
                            <val>1</val>
                        </valueItem>
                        <valueItem>
                            <label>active</label>
                            <val>2</val>
                        </valueItem>
                    </valueList>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-only</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This parameter describes the initial value of&lt;br&gt;the administrative status, ifAdminStatus, of&lt;br&gt;this LLC port at last port start-up.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcPortOperLastModifyTime</objectName>
                <objectId>3</objectId>
                <parent>llcPortOperEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>TimeTicks</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-only</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object describes the value of sysUpTime&lt;br&gt;when this port definition was last modified.&lt;br&gt;If the port has not been modified, then this&lt;br&gt;value shall be zero.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcPortOperLastFailTime</objectName>
                <objectId>4</objectId>
                <parent>llcPortOperEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>TimeTicks</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-only</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object describes the value of sysUpTime&lt;br&gt;when this LLC port last failed.  If the port&lt;br&gt;has not failed, then this value shall be zero.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcPortOperLastFailCause</objectName>
                <objectId>5</objectId>
                <parent>llcPortOperEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>INTEGER</type>
                    <valueList>
                        <valueItem>
                            <label>undefined</label>
                            <val>1</val>
                        </valueItem>
                        <valueItem>
                            <label>physical</label>
                            <val>2</val>
                        </valueItem>
                    </valueList>
                    <defaultValue>undefined</defaultValue>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-only</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This enumerated object describes the cause of&lt;br&gt;the last failure of this LLC port.  If the port&lt;br&gt;has not failed, then this object has a value of&lt;br&gt;undefined(1).</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcPortStatsTable</objectName>
                <objectId>3</objectId>
                <parent>llcPortGroup</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <sequence>LlcPortStatsEntry</sequence>
                </syntax>
                <access>not-accessible</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>Each entry in this table contains statistics&lt;br&gt;for a specific LLC port.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcPortStatsEntry</objectName>
                <objectId>1</objectId>
                <parent>llcPortStatsTable</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>LlcPortStatsEntry</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>not-accessible</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>A list of statistics for an LLC port.</description>
                <indices>
                    <index>ifIndex</index>
                </indices>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcPortStatsPhysicalFailures</objectName>
                <objectId>1</objectId>
                <parent>llcPortStatsEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>Counter32</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-only</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object reflects the total number of times&lt;br&gt;this port has failed due to its physical media&lt;br&gt;since port startup.  At port startup time, this&lt;br&gt;object must be initialized to zero.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcPortStatsPollsIn</objectName>
                <objectId>2</objectId>
                <parent>llcPortStatsEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>Counter32</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-only</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object reflects the total number of polls&lt;br&gt;received by this port since the port was&lt;br&gt;created.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcPortStatsPollsOut</objectName>
                <objectId>3</objectId>
                <parent>llcPortStatsEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>Counter32</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-only</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object reflects the total number of polls&lt;br&gt;sent by this port since the port was created.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcPortStatsPollRspsIn</objectName>
                <objectId>4</objectId>
                <parent>llcPortStatsEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>Counter32</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-only</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object reflects the total number of poll&lt;br&gt;responses received by this port since the port&lt;br&gt;was created.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcPortStatsPollRspsOut</objectName>
                <objectId>5</objectId>
                <parent>llcPortStatsEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>Counter32</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-only</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object reflects the total number of poll&lt;br&gt;responses sent by this port since the port was&lt;br&gt;created.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcPortStatsLocalBusies</objectName>
                <objectId>6</objectId>
                <parent>llcPortStatsEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>Counter32</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-only</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object reflects the total number of&lt;br&gt;times that the local link stations on this&lt;br&gt;port have entered a busy state (RNR).  This&lt;br&gt;object is initialized to zero when the port is&lt;br&gt;created.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcPortStatsRemoteBusies</objectName>
                <objectId>7</objectId>
                <parent>llcPortStatsEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>Counter32</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-only</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object reflects the total number of&lt;br&gt;times that the adjacent (i.e. remote) link&lt;br&gt;stations on this port have entered a busy&lt;br&gt;state (RNR).  This object is initialized to&lt;br&gt;zero when the port is created.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcPortStatsIFramesIn</objectName>
                <objectId>8</objectId>
                <parent>llcPortStatsEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>Counter32</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-only</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object reflects the total number of&lt;br&gt;I-Frames that have been received by link&lt;br&gt;stations on this port.  This object is&lt;br&gt;initialized to zero when the port is created.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcPortStatsIFramesOut</objectName>
                <objectId>9</objectId>
                <parent>llcPortStatsEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>Counter32</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-only</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object reflects the total number of&lt;br&gt;I-Frames that have been transmitted by link&lt;br&gt;stations on this port.  This object is&lt;br&gt;initialized to zero when the port is created.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcPortStatsOctetsIn</objectName>
                <objectId>10</objectId>
                <parent>llcPortStatsEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>Counter32</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-only</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object reflects the total octets&lt;br&gt;received from adjacent link stations on this&lt;br&gt;port.  This object covers the address,&lt;br&gt;control, and information field of I-Frames&lt;br&gt;only.  This object is initialized to zero when&lt;br&gt;the port is created.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcPortStatsOctetsOut</objectName>
                <objectId>11</objectId>
                <parent>llcPortStatsEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>Counter32</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-only</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object reflects the total octets&lt;br&gt;transmitted to adjacent link stations on this&lt;br&gt;port.  This object covers the address,&lt;br&gt;control, and information field of I-Frames&lt;br&gt;only.  This object is initialized to zero when&lt;br&gt;the port is created.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcPortStatsProtocolErrs</objectName>
                <objectId>12</objectId>
                <parent>llcPortStatsEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>Counter32</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-only</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object reflects the total number of&lt;br&gt;times that the link stations on this port have&lt;br&gt;deactivated the link as a result of having&lt;br&gt;received a protocol violation from the&lt;br&gt;adjacent link station.  This object is&lt;br&gt;initialized to zero when the port is created.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcPortStatsActivityTOs</objectName>
                <objectId>13</objectId>
                <parent>llcPortStatsEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>Counter32</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-only</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object reflects the total number of&lt;br&gt;times that the link stations on this port&lt;br&gt;have deactivated the link as a result of no&lt;br&gt;activity on the link.  This object is&lt;br&gt;initialized to zero when the port is created.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcPortStatsRetriesExps</objectName>
                <objectId>14</objectId>
                <parent>llcPortStatsEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>Counter32</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-only</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object reflects the total number of&lt;br&gt;times that the link stations on this port&lt;br&gt;have deactivated the link as a result of a&lt;br&gt;retry sequence being exhausted.  This object&lt;br&gt;is initialized to zero when the port is&lt;br&gt;created.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcPortStatsRetransmitsIn</objectName>
                <objectId>15</objectId>
                <parent>llcPortStatsEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>Counter32</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-only</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object reflects the total number of&lt;br&gt;I-Frames retransmitted by remote link stations&lt;br&gt;for all link stations on this port.  This&lt;br&gt;object is initialized to zero when the port is&lt;br&gt;created.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcPortStatsRetransmitsOut</objectName>
                <objectId>16</objectId>
                <parent>llcPortStatsEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>Counter32</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-only</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object reflects the total number of&lt;br&gt;I-Frames retransmitted by all local link&lt;br&gt;stations on this port.  This object is&lt;br&gt;initialized to zero when the port is created.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcSapAdminTable</objectName>
                <objectId>1</objectId>
                <parent>llcSapGroup</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <sequence>LlcSapAdminEntry</sequence>
                </syntax>
                <access>not-accessible</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This table contains objects that can be&lt;br&gt;changed to manage a local SAP.    Changing one&lt;br&gt;of these parameters may take effect in the&lt;br&gt;operating SAP immediately or may wait until the&lt;br&gt;interface is restarted depending on the details&lt;br&gt;of the implementation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most of the objects in this read-write table&lt;br&gt;have corresponding read-only objects in the&lt;br&gt;llcSapOperTable that return the current&lt;br&gt;operating value.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The operating values may be different from&lt;br&gt;these configured values if  a configured&lt;br&gt;parameter was changed after the interface was&lt;br&gt;started.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcSapAdminEntry</objectName>
                <objectId>1</objectId>
                <parent>llcSapAdminTable</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>LlcSapAdminEntry</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>not-accessible</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>A list of configured values for a local SAP.</description>
                <indices>
                    <index>ifIndex</index>
                    <index>llcSapNumber</index>
                </indices>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcSapNumber</objectName>
                <objectId>1</objectId>
                <parent>llcSapAdminEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>INTEGER(1..255)</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-write</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>The address of this local SAP.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcSapAdminState</objectName>
                <objectId>2</objectId>
                <parent>llcSapAdminEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>INTEGER</type>
                    <valueList>
                        <valueItem>
                            <label>disabled</label>
                            <val>1</val>
                        </valueItem>
                        <valueItem>
                            <label>enabled</label>
                            <val>2</val>
                        </valueItem>
                    </valueList>
                    <defaultValue>enabled</defaultValue>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-write</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This parameter controls the desired state of&lt;br&gt;this local SAP.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcSapAdminMaxIPDUOctetsSend</objectName>
                <objectId>3</objectId>
                <parent>llcSapAdminEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>Integer32</type>
                    <defaultValue>0</defaultValue>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-write</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object denotes the default maximum I PDU&lt;br&gt;size, in octets, that LLCs on this SAP may send&lt;br&gt;to their remote connection component partners.&lt;br&gt;This count is referred to as 'N1' in the IEEE&lt;br&gt;802.2 specification [??].&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A zero value for this object indicates that the&lt;br&gt;port default, llcPortAdminMaxIPDUOctetsSend,&lt;br&gt;shall be used as the SAP default.  This SAP&lt;br&gt;default value may be overridden by a non-zero&lt;br&gt;value in the llcCcAdminMaxIPDUOctetsSend&lt;br&gt;object.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;At connection setup, the remote LLC may send,&lt;br&gt;using an XID frame, the maximum I PDU size&lt;br&gt;which it is prepared to receive. If so, an&lt;br&gt;implementation may choose to override the&lt;br&gt;administered maximum PDU size with the&lt;br&gt;dynamically learned value and should reflect&lt;br&gt;this in the llcCcOperMaxIPDUOctetsSend object&lt;br&gt;for the connection component.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The I PDU size includes all octets in a frame,&lt;br&gt;excluding framing characters, the MAC header&lt;br&gt;and link link header.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcSapAdminMaxIPDUOctetsRcv</objectName>
                <objectId>4</objectId>
                <parent>llcSapAdminEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>Integer32</type>
                    <defaultValue>0</defaultValue>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-write</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object denotes the default maximum I PDU&lt;br&gt;size, in octets, that LLCs on this SAP can&lt;br&gt;expect to receive from their remote LLC&lt;br&gt;partners. This count is referred to as 'N1' in&lt;br&gt;the IEEE 802.2 specification [??]&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A zero value for this object indicates that the&lt;br&gt;port default, llcPortAdminMaxIPDUOctetsRcv,&lt;br&gt;shall be used as the SAP default.  This SAP&lt;br&gt;default value may be overridden by a non-zero&lt;br&gt;value in the llcCcAdminMaxIPDUOctetsRcv&lt;br&gt;object.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;At connection setup, an implementation may&lt;br&gt;choose to send this value to the remote LLC,&lt;br&gt;using an XID frame.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The I PDU size includes all octets in a frame&lt;br&gt;with the exception of the framing characters,&lt;br&gt;the MAC header and the link header.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcSapAdminMaxUnackedIPDUsSend</objectName>
                <objectId>5</objectId>
                <parent>llcSapAdminEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>INTEGER(1..127)</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-write</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object denotes the default maximum&lt;br&gt;consequetive unacknowledged I PDU frames that&lt;br&gt;LLCs on this SAP may send to their remote LLC&lt;br&gt;partners. This count is referred to as 'k' in&lt;br&gt;the IEEE 802.2 specification [??].&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A zero value for this object indicates that the&lt;br&gt;port default, llcPortAdminMaxUnackedIPDUsSend,&lt;br&gt;shall be used as the SAP default.  This SAP&lt;br&gt;default value may be overridden by a non-zero&lt;br&gt;value in the llcCcAdminMaxUnackedIPDUsSend&lt;br&gt;object.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;At connection setup, the remote LLC may send,&lt;br&gt;using an XID frame, the maximum number of&lt;br&gt;unacknowledged I PDUs which it is prepared to&lt;br&gt;receive. If so, an implementation may choose to&lt;br&gt;override the administered maximum number of&lt;br&gt;unacknowledged PDUs with the dynamicly learned&lt;br&gt;value and should reflect this in the&lt;br&gt;llcCcOperMaxUnackedIPDUsSend object for the&lt;br&gt;connection component.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcSapAdminMaxUnackedIPDUsRcv</objectName>
                <objectId>6</objectId>
                <parent>llcSapAdminEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>INTEGER(1..127)</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-write</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object denotes the default maximum number&lt;br&gt;of unacknowledged I PDUs that LLCs on this SAP&lt;br&gt;can expect to receive from their remote LLC&lt;br&gt;partners. This count is referred to as 'k' in&lt;br&gt;the IEEE 802.2 specification [??].&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A zero value for this object indicates that the&lt;br&gt;port default, llcPortAdminMaxUnackedIPDUsRcv,&lt;br&gt;shall be used as the SAP default.  This SAP&lt;br&gt;default value may be overridden by a non-zero&lt;br&gt;value in the llcCcAdminMaxUnackedIPDUsRcv&lt;br&gt;object.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;At connection setup, an implementation may&lt;br&gt;choose to send this value to the remote LLC,&lt;br&gt;using an XID frame.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcSapAdminMaxRetransmits</objectName>
                <objectId>7</objectId>
                <parent>llcSapAdminEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>INTEGER</type>
                    <defaultValue>0</defaultValue>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-write</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object denotes the default value for the&lt;br&gt;maximum number of times that LLCs on this SAP&lt;br&gt;shall retry PDUs following the expiration of&lt;br&gt;the acknowledgement timer, the P-bit timer or&lt;br&gt;the reject timer. When these retries are&lt;br&gt;exhausted, thelink shall be declared inactive.&lt;br&gt;This count is referred to as 'N2' in the IEEE&lt;br&gt;802.2 specification [??].&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A zero value for this object indicates that the&lt;br&gt;port default, llcPortAdminMaxRetransmits, shall&lt;br&gt;be used as the SAP default.  This SAP default&lt;br&gt;value may be overridden by a non-zero value in&lt;br&gt;the llcCcAdminMaxRetransmits.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcSapAdminAckTimer</objectName>
                <objectId>8</objectId>
                <parent>llcSapAdminEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>TimeTicks</type>
                    <defaultValue>0</defaultValue>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-write</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object denotes the default value for the&lt;br&gt;time interval during which the LLCs on this SAP&lt;br&gt;shall expect to receive either:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1) an acknowledgement to one or more&lt;br&gt;outstanding I PDUs.  or 2) a response PDU to an&lt;br&gt;unnumbered command PDU.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The expiration of this timer shall cause the&lt;br&gt;frame unacknowledged frames to be retransmitted&lt;br&gt;(up to N2 times).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A zero value for this object indicates that the&lt;br&gt;port default, llcPortAdminAckTimer, shall be&lt;br&gt;used as the SAP default.  This SAP default&lt;br&gt;value may be overridden by a non-zero value in&lt;br&gt;the llcCcAdminAckTimer.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcSapAdminPbitTimer</objectName>
                <objectId>9</objectId>
                <parent>llcSapAdminEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>TimeTicks</type>
                    <defaultValue>0</defaultValue>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-write</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object denotes the default value for the&lt;br&gt;time interval during which the LLCs on this&lt;br&gt;port shall expect to receive a PDU with the F&lt;br&gt;bit set to '1' in response to a Type 2 command&lt;br&gt;with the P bit set to '1'.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The expiration of this timer shall cause the&lt;br&gt;REJ PDU to be retransmitted (up to N2 times).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A zero value for this object indicates that the&lt;br&gt;port default, llcPortAdminPbitTimer, shall be&lt;br&gt;used as the SAP default.  This SAP default&lt;br&gt;value may be overridden by a non-zero value in&lt;br&gt;the llcCcAdminPbitTimer.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcSapAdminRejTimer</objectName>
                <objectId>10</objectId>
                <parent>llcSapAdminEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>TimeTicks</type>
                    <defaultValue>0</defaultValue>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-write</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object denotes the default value for the&lt;br&gt;time interval during which the LLCs on this SAP&lt;br&gt;shall expect to receive a reply to a REJ PDU.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The expiration of this timer shall cause the&lt;br&gt;REJ PDU to be retransmitted (up to N2 times).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A zero value for this object indicates that the&lt;br&gt;port default, llcPortAdminRejTimer, shall be&lt;br&gt;used as the SAP default.  This SAP default&lt;br&gt;value may be overridden by a non-zero value in&lt;br&gt;the llcCcAdminRejTimer.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcSapAdminBusyTimer</objectName>
                <objectId>11</objectId>
                <parent>llcSapAdminEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>TimeTicks</type>
                    <defaultValue>0</defaultValue>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-write</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object denotes the default value for the&lt;br&gt;time interval during which the LLCs on this SAP&lt;br&gt;shall expect to receive an indication that a&lt;br&gt;busy condition at the remote LLC has cleared.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The expiration of this timer shall cause the&lt;br&gt;link to be declared inactive.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A zero value for this object indicates that the&lt;br&gt;port default, llcPortAdminBusyTimer, shall be&lt;br&gt;used as the SAP default.  This SAP default&lt;br&gt;value may be overridden by a non-zero value in&lt;br&gt;the llcCcAdminBusyTimer.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcSapAdminInactTimer</objectName>
                <objectId>12</objectId>
                <parent>llcSapAdminEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>TimeTicks</type>
                    <defaultValue>0</defaultValue>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-write</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object denotes the default value for the&lt;br&gt;time interval during which the LLCs on this SAP&lt;br&gt;shall expect to receive any PDU from the remote&lt;br&gt;LLC.  This function is not described in the&lt;br&gt;IEEE 802.2 specification [??] but is widely&lt;br&gt;implemented.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The expiration of this timer shall cause the&lt;br&gt;local LLC to send a PDU to the remote LLC with&lt;br&gt;the P bit set to '1'.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A zero value for this object indicates that the&lt;br&gt;port default, llcPortAdminInactTimer, shall be&lt;br&gt;used as the SAP default.  This SAP default&lt;br&gt;value may be overridden by a non-zero value in&lt;br&gt;the llcCcAdminInactTimer.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Any value for this object less than or equal to&lt;br&gt;the acknowledgement timer shall mean that the&lt;br&gt;timer is not used.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcSapAdminDelayAckCount</objectName>
                <objectId>13</objectId>
                <parent>llcSapAdminEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>INTEGER</type>
                    <defaultValue>0</defaultValue>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-write</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object denotes the default value for the&lt;br&gt;maximum number of consequetive I PDUs which the&lt;br&gt;LLCs on this SAP shall receive during the&lt;br&gt;interval defined by llcCcOperDelayTimer without&lt;br&gt;sending an immediate acknowledgement.  This&lt;br&gt;must be less than or equal to the value of&lt;br&gt;llcCcOperMaxUnackIPDURcv. This function is not&lt;br&gt;described in the IEEE 802.2 specification [??]&lt;br&gt;but is widely implemented.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A zero value for this object indicates that the&lt;br&gt;port default, llcPortAdminDelayAck, shall be&lt;br&gt;used as the SAP default.  This SAP default&lt;br&gt;value may be overridden by a non-zero value in&lt;br&gt;the llcCcAdminDelayAckCount.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A value of one indicates that acknowledgments&lt;br&gt;will be sent immediately and that the value of&lt;br&gt;llcSapAdminDelayAckTimer shall be ignored.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcSapAdminDelayAckTimer</objectName>
                <objectId>14</objectId>
                <parent>llcSapAdminEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>TimeTicks</type>
                    <defaultValue>0</defaultValue>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-write</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object denotes the default value for the&lt;br&gt;time interval during which the LLCs on this SAP&lt;br&gt;shall delay acknowledgment of one or more I&lt;br&gt;PDUs (up to the value of&lt;br&gt;llcCcOperDelayAckCount). This function is not&lt;br&gt;described in the IEEE 802.2 specification [??]&lt;br&gt;but is widely implemented.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The expiration of this timer shall cause the&lt;br&gt;local LLC to acknowledge all unacknowledged I&lt;br&gt;PDUs.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This object is associated with the&lt;br&gt;llcSapAdminDelayAckCount object and is only&lt;br&gt;defined if that object has a value greater than&lt;br&gt;one.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcSapOperTable</objectName>
                <objectId>2</objectId>
                <parent>llcSapGroup</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <sequence>LlcSapOperEntry</sequence>
                </syntax>
                <access>not-accessible</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This table contains objects that reflect the&lt;br&gt;current operational parameters of a local SAP.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many of these objects in this table have&lt;br&gt;corresponding objects in the llcSapAdminTable.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcSapOperEntry</objectName>
                <objectId>1</objectId>
                <parent>llcSapOperTable</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>LlcSapOperEntry</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>not-accessible</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>A list of configured values for a local SAP.</description>
                <indices>
                    <index>ifIndex</index>
                    <index>llcSapNumber</index>
                </indices>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcSapOperStatus</objectName>
                <objectId>1</objectId>
                <parent>llcSapOperEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>INTEGER</type>
                    <valueList>
                        <valueItem>
                            <label>inactive</label>
                            <val>1</val>
                        </valueItem>
                        <valueItem>
                            <label>active</label>
                            <val>2</val>
                        </valueItem>
                    </valueList>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-only</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This parameter describes the actual state of&lt;br&gt;this local SAP.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcSapStatsTable</objectName>
                <objectId>3</objectId>
                <parent>llcSapGroup</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <sequence>LlcSapStatsEntry</sequence>
                </syntax>
                <access>not-accessible</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This table contains objects that reflect the&lt;br&gt;current operational parameters of a local SAP.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many of these objects in this table have&lt;br&gt;corresponding objects in the llcSapAdminTable.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcSapStatsEntry</objectName>
                <objectId>1</objectId>
                <parent>llcSapStatsTable</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>LlcSapStatsEntry</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>not-accessible</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>A list of configured values for a local SAP.</description>
                <indices>
                    <index>ifIndex</index>
                    <index>llcSapNumber</index>
                </indices>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcSapStatsTESTsIn</objectName>
                <objectId>1</objectId>
                <parent>llcSapStatsEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>Counter32</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-only</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object reflects the total number of TEST&lt;br&gt;frames (both commands and responses) received on&lt;br&gt;a local SAP.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcSapStatsTESTsOut</objectName>
                <objectId>2</objectId>
                <parent>llcSapStatsEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>Counter32</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-only</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object reflects the total number of TEST&lt;br&gt;frames (both commands and responses) sent on&lt;br&gt;a local SAP.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcSapStatsXIDsIn</objectName>
                <objectId>3</objectId>
                <parent>llcSapStatsEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>Counter32</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-only</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object reflects the total number of XID&lt;br&gt;frames (both commands and responses) received on&lt;br&gt;a local SAP.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcSapStatsXIDsOut</objectName>
                <objectId>4</objectId>
                <parent>llcSapStatsEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>Counter32</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-only</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object reflects the total number of XID&lt;br&gt;frames (both commands and responses) sent on&lt;br&gt;a local SAP.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcSapStatsUIFramesIn</objectName>
                <objectId>5</objectId>
                <parent>llcSapStatsEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>Counter32</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-only</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object reflects the total number of&lt;br&gt;unnumbered information (UI) frames received on&lt;br&gt;a local SAP.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcSapStatsUIFramesOut</objectName>
                <objectId>6</objectId>
                <parent>llcSapStatsEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>Counter32</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-only</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object reflects the total number of&lt;br&gt;unnumbered information (UI) frames sent on a&lt;br&gt;local SAP.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcCcAdminTable</objectName>
                <objectId>1</objectId>
                <parent>llcCcGroup</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <sequence>LlcCcAdminEntry</sequence>
                </syntax>
                <access>not-accessible</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This table contains objects that can be&lt;br&gt;changed to manage an LLC link station.&lt;br&gt;Changing one of these parameters may take&lt;br&gt;effect in the operating link immediately or may&lt;br&gt;wait until the link is restarted depending on&lt;br&gt;the details of the implementation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The entries in llcCcAdminTable can be created&lt;br&gt;either by an agent or a management station. The&lt;br&gt;management station can create an entry in&lt;br&gt;llcCcAdminTable by setting the appropriate&lt;br&gt;value in llcCcAdminRowStatus.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most of the objects in this read-create table&lt;br&gt;have corresponding read-only objects in the&lt;br&gt;llcCcOperTable that reflect the current&lt;br&gt;operating value.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The operating values may be different from&lt;br&gt;these configured values if changed by XID&lt;br&gt;negotiation or if a configured parameter was&lt;br&gt;changed after the link was started.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcCcAdminEntry</objectName>
                <objectId>1</objectId>
                <parent>llcCcAdminTable</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>LlcCcAdminEntry</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>not-accessible</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>A list of configured values for an LLC link&lt;br&gt;station.</description>
                <indices>
                    <index>ifIndex</index>
                    <index>llcCcLSap</index>
                    <index>llcCcRSap</index>
                    <index>llcCcRMac</index>
                    <index>llcCcLMac</index>
                </indices>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcCcLSap</objectName>
                <objectId>1</objectId>
                <parent>llcCcAdminEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>INTEGER(1..255)</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-write</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This value is the address of the local SAP&lt;br&gt;for this Connection Component.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcCcRSap</objectName>
                <objectId>2</objectId>
                <parent>llcCcAdminEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>INTEGER(1..255)</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-write</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This value is the address of the remote SAP&lt;br&gt;for this Connection Component.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcCcLMac</objectName>
                <objectId>3</objectId>
                <parent>llcCcAdminEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>OCTET STRING(SIZE(6))</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-write</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This value is the local MAC address for this&lt;br&gt;Connection Component.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcCcRMac</objectName>
                <objectId>4</objectId>
                <parent>llcCcAdminEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>OCTET STRING(SIZE(6))</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-write</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This value is the remote MAC address for this&lt;br&gt;Connection Component.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcCcAdminState</objectName>
                <objectId>5</objectId>
                <parent>llcCcAdminEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>INTEGER</type>
                    <valueList>
                        <valueItem>
                            <label>disabled</label>
                            <val>1</val>
                        </valueItem>
                        <valueItem>
                            <label>enabled</label>
                            <val>2</val>
                        </valueItem>
                    </valueList>
                    <defaultValue>enabled</defaultValue>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-write</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object controls the desired state of the&lt;br&gt;LLC connection.  The managed system shall attempt&lt;br&gt;to keep the operational state, llcCcOperState,&lt;br&gt;consistent with this value.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcCcAdminMaxIPDUOctetsSend</objectName>
                <objectId>6</objectId>
                <parent>llcCcAdminEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>Integer32</type>
                    <defaultValue>0</defaultValue>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-write</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object denotes the maximum I PDU size, in&lt;br&gt;octets, that this LLC SAP may send to its&lt;br&gt;remote connection component partner. This count&lt;br&gt;is referred to as 'N1' in the IEEE 802.2&lt;br&gt;specification [??].&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This object contains an administrative value&lt;br&gt;which will be applied the next time this&lt;br&gt;connection is established.  A zero value for&lt;br&gt;this object indicates that the SAP default,&lt;br&gt;llcSapAdminMaxIPDUOctetsSend, shall be used.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;At connection setup, the remote LLC may send,&lt;br&gt;using an XID frame, the maximum I PDU size&lt;br&gt;which it is prepared to receive. If so, an&lt;br&gt;implementation may choose to override the&lt;br&gt;administered maximum PDU size with the&lt;br&gt;dynamically learned value and should reflect&lt;br&gt;this in the llcCcOperMaxIPDUOctetsSend object&lt;br&gt;for the connection component.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The I PDU size includes all octets in a frame,&lt;br&gt;excluding framing characters, the MAC header&lt;br&gt;and link link header.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcCcAdminMaxIPDUOctetsRcv</objectName>
                <objectId>7</objectId>
                <parent>llcCcAdminEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>Integer32</type>
                    <defaultValue>0</defaultValue>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-write</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object denotes the maximum I PDU size,in&lt;br&gt;octets, that this LLC can expect to receive&lt;br&gt;from its remote LLC partner. This count is&lt;br&gt;referred to as 'N1' in the IEEE 802.2&lt;br&gt;specification [??]&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This object contains an administrative value&lt;br&gt;which will be applied the next time this&lt;br&gt;connection is established.  A zero value for&lt;br&gt;this object indicates that the SAP default,&lt;br&gt;llcSapAdminMaxIPDUOctetsRcv, shall be used.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;At connection setup, an implementation may&lt;br&gt;choose to send this value to the remote LLC,&lt;br&gt;using an XID frame.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The I PDU size includes all octets in a frame&lt;br&gt;with the exception of the framing characters,&lt;br&gt;the MAC header and the link header.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcCcAdminMaxUnackedIPDUsSend</objectName>
                <objectId>8</objectId>
                <parent>llcCcAdminEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>INTEGER(1..127)</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-write</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object denotes the maximum consequetive&lt;br&gt;unacknowledged I PDU frames that this LLC may&lt;br&gt;send to its remote LLC partner. This count is&lt;br&gt;referred to as 'k' in the IEEE 802.2&lt;br&gt;specification [??].&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This object contains an administrative value&lt;br&gt;which will be applied the next time this&lt;br&gt;connection is established.  A zero value for&lt;br&gt;this object indicates that the SAP default,&lt;br&gt;llcSapAdminMaxUnackedIPDUsSend, shall be used.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;At connection setup, the remote LLC may send,&lt;br&gt;using an XID frame, the maximum number of&lt;br&gt;unacknowledged I PDUs which it is prepared to&lt;br&gt;receive. If so, an implementation may choose to&lt;br&gt;override the administered maximum number of&lt;br&gt;unacknowledged PDUs with the dynamicly learned&lt;br&gt;value and should reflect this in the&lt;br&gt;llcCcOperMaxUnackedIPDUsSend object for the&lt;br&gt;connection component.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcCcAdminMaxUnackedIPDUsRcv</objectName>
                <objectId>9</objectId>
                <parent>llcCcAdminEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>INTEGER(1..127)</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-write</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object denotes the maximum number of&lt;br&gt;unacknowledged I PDUs that this LLC can expect&lt;br&gt;to receive from its remote LLC partner. This&lt;br&gt;count is referred to as 'k' in the IEEE 802.2&lt;br&gt;specification [??].&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This object contains an administrative value&lt;br&gt;which will be applied the next time this&lt;br&gt;connection is established.  A zero value for&lt;br&gt;this object indicates that the SAP default,&lt;br&gt;llcSapAdminMaxUnackedIPDUsRcv, shall be used.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;At connection setup, an implementation may&lt;br&gt;choose to send this value to the remote LLC,&lt;br&gt;using an XID frame.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcCcAdminMaxRetransmits</objectName>
                <objectId>10</objectId>
                <parent>llcCcAdminEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>INTEGER</type>
                    <defaultValue>0</defaultValue>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-write</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object denotes the value for the maximum&lt;br&gt;number of times that this LLC shall retry PDUs&lt;br&gt;following the expiration of the acknowledgement&lt;br&gt;timer, the P-bit timer or the reject timer.&lt;br&gt;When these retries are exhausted, the link&lt;br&gt;shall be declared inactive.  This count is&lt;br&gt;referred to as 'N2' in the IEEE 802.2&lt;br&gt;specification [??].&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This object contains an administrative value&lt;br&gt;which will be applied the next time this&lt;br&gt;connection is established.  A zero value for&lt;br&gt;this object indicates that the SAP default,&lt;br&gt;llcSapAdminMaxRetransmits, shall be used.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcCcAdminAckTimer</objectName>
                <objectId>11</objectId>
                <parent>llcCcAdminEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>TimeTicks</type>
                    <defaultValue>0</defaultValue>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-write</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object denotes the value for the time&lt;br&gt;interval during which this LLC shall expect to&lt;br&gt;receive either:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1) an acknowledgement to one or more&lt;br&gt;outstanding I PDUs.  or 2) a response PDU to an&lt;br&gt;unnumbered command PDU.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The expiration of this timer shall cause the&lt;br&gt;frame unacknowledged frames to be retransmitted&lt;br&gt;(up to N2 times).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This object contains an administrative value&lt;br&gt;which will be applied the next time this&lt;br&gt;connection is established.  A zero value for&lt;br&gt;this object indicates that the SAP default,&lt;br&gt;llcSapAdminAckTimer, shall be used.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcCcAdminPbitTimer</objectName>
                <objectId>12</objectId>
                <parent>llcCcAdminEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>TimeTicks</type>
                    <defaultValue>0</defaultValue>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-write</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object denotes the value for the time&lt;br&gt;interval during which this LLC shall expect to&lt;br&gt;receive a PDU with the F bit set to '1' in&lt;br&gt;response to a Type 2 command with the P bit set&lt;br&gt;to '1'.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The expiration of this timer shall cause the&lt;br&gt;REJ PDU to be retransmitted (up to N2 times).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This object contains an administrative value&lt;br&gt;which will be applied the next time this&lt;br&gt;connection is established.  A zero value for&lt;br&gt;this object indicates that the SAP default,&lt;br&gt;llcSapAdminPbitTimer, shall be used.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcCcAdminRejTimer</objectName>
                <objectId>13</objectId>
                <parent>llcCcAdminEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>TimeTicks</type>
                    <defaultValue>0</defaultValue>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-write</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object denotes the value for the time&lt;br&gt;interval during which this LLC shall expect to&lt;br&gt;receive a reply to a REJ PDU.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The expiration of this timer shall cause the&lt;br&gt;REJ PDU to be retransmitted (up to N2 times).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This object contains an administrative value&lt;br&gt;which will be applied the next time this&lt;br&gt;connection is established.  A zero value for&lt;br&gt;this object indicates that the SAP default,&lt;br&gt;llcSapAdminRejTimer, shall be used.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcCcAdminBusyTimer</objectName>
                <objectId>14</objectId>
                <parent>llcCcAdminEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>TimeTicks</type>
                    <defaultValue>0</defaultValue>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-write</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object denotes the value for the time&lt;br&gt;interval during which this LLC shall expect to&lt;br&gt;receive an indication that a busy condition at&lt;br&gt;the remote LLC has cleared.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The expiration of this timer shall cause the&lt;br&gt;link to be declared inactive.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This object contains an administrative value&lt;br&gt;which will be applied the next time this&lt;br&gt;connection is established.  A zero value for&lt;br&gt;this object indicates that the SAP default,&lt;br&gt;llcSapAdminBusyTimer, shall be used.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcCcAdminInactTimer</objectName>
                <objectId>15</objectId>
                <parent>llcCcAdminEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>TimeTicks</type>
                    <defaultValue>0</defaultValue>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-write</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object denotes the value for the time&lt;br&gt;interval during which this LLC shall expect to&lt;br&gt;receive any PDU from the remote LLC.  This&lt;br&gt;function is not described in the IEEE 802.2&lt;br&gt;specification [??] but is widely implemented.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The expiration of this timer shall cause the&lt;br&gt;local LLC to send a PDU to the remote LLC with&lt;br&gt;the P bit set to '1'.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This object contains an administrative value&lt;br&gt;which will be applied the next time this&lt;br&gt;connection is established.  A zero value for&lt;br&gt;this object indicates that the SAP default,&lt;br&gt;llcSapAdminInactTimer, shall be used.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Any value for this object less than or equal to&lt;br&gt;the acknowledgement timer shall mean that the&lt;br&gt;timer is not used.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcCcAdminDelayAckCount</objectName>
                <objectId>16</objectId>
                <parent>llcCcAdminEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>INTEGER</type>
                    <defaultValue>0</defaultValue>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-write</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object denotes the value for the maximum&lt;br&gt;number of consequetive I PDUs which this LLC&lt;br&gt;shall receive during the interval defined by&lt;br&gt;llcCcOperDelayTimer without sending an&lt;br&gt;immediate acknowledgement.  This must be less&lt;br&gt;than or equal to the value of&lt;br&gt;llcCcOperMaxUnackIPDURcv. This function is not&lt;br&gt;described in the IEEE 802.2 specification [??]&lt;br&gt;but is widely implemented.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This object contains an administrative value&lt;br&gt;which will be applied the next time this&lt;br&gt;connection is established.  A zero value for&lt;br&gt;this object indicates that the SAP default,&lt;br&gt;llcSapAdminDelayAck, shall be used.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A value of one indicates that acknowledgments&lt;br&gt;will be sent immediately and that the value of&lt;br&gt;llcCcAdminDelayAckTimer shall be ignored.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcCcAdminDelayAckTimer</objectName>
                <objectId>17</objectId>
                <parent>llcCcAdminEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>TimeTicks</type>
                    <defaultValue>0</defaultValue>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-write</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object denotes the value for the time&lt;br&gt;interval during which this LLC shall delay&lt;br&gt;acknowledgment of one or more I PDUs (up to the&lt;br&gt;value of llcCcOperDelayAckCount). This function&lt;br&gt;is not described in the IEEE 802.2&lt;br&gt;specification [??] but is widely implemented.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The expiration of this timer shall cause the&lt;br&gt;local LLC to acknowledge all unacknowledged I&lt;br&gt;PDUs.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This object contains an administrative value&lt;br&gt;which will be applied the next time this&lt;br&gt;connection is established.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This object is associated with the&lt;br&gt;llcCcAdminDelayAckCount object and is only&lt;br&gt;defined if that object has a value greater than&lt;br&gt;one.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcCcAdminRowStatus</objectName>
                <objectId>18</objectId>
                <parent>llcCcAdminEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>RowStatus</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-write</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object is used by a management station to&lt;br&gt;create or delete the row entry in&lt;br&gt;llcCcAdminTable following the RowStatus textual&lt;br&gt;convention.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Upon successful creation of the row, an agent&lt;br&gt;automatically creates a corresponding entry in&lt;br&gt;the llcCcOperTable with llcCcOperState equal to&lt;br&gt;'discontacted (1)'.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcCcOperTable</objectName>
                <objectId>2</objectId>
                <parent>llcCcGroup</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <sequence>LlcCcOperEntry</sequence>
                </syntax>
                <access>not-accessible</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This table contains current LLC link&lt;br&gt;parameters.  Many of these objects have&lt;br&gt;corresponding objects in the&lt;br&gt;llcCcAdminTable.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcCcOperEntry</objectName>
                <objectId>1</objectId>
                <parent>llcCcOperTable</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>LlcCcOperEntry</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>not-accessible</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>A list of status and control values for an&lt;br&gt;LLC link station.</description>
                <indices>
                    <index>ifIndex</index>
                    <index>llcCcLSap</index>
                    <index>llcCcRSap</index>
                    <index>llcCcRMac</index>
                    <index>llcCcLMac</index>
                </indices>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcCcOperRole</objectName>
                <objectId>1</objectId>
                <parent>llcCcOperEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>INTEGER</type>
                    <valueList>
                        <valueItem>
                            <label>primary</label>
                            <val>1</val>
                        </valueItem>
                        <valueItem>
                            <label>secondary</label>
                            <val>2</val>
                        </valueItem>
                        <valueItem>
                            <label>undefined</label>
                            <val>3</val>
                        </valueItem>
                    </valueList>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-only</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object reflects the current role that the link&lt;br&gt;station is assuming.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcCcOperState</objectName>
                <objectId>2</objectId>
                <parent>llcCcOperEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>INTEGER</type>
                    <valueList>
                        <valueItem>
                            <label>discontacted</label>
                            <val>1</val>
                        </valueItem>
                        <valueItem>
                            <label>contactPending</label>
                            <val>2</val>
                        </valueItem>
                        <valueItem>
                            <label>contacted</label>
                            <val>3</val>
                        </valueItem>
                        <valueItem>
                            <label>discontactPending</label>
                            <val>4</val>
                        </valueItem>
                    </valueList>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-only</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object describes the operational state of&lt;br&gt;the LLC connection.  The managed system shall&lt;br&gt;attempt to keep this value consistent with the&lt;br&gt;administered state, llcCcAdminState</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcCcOperMaxIPDUOctetsSend</objectName>
                <objectId>3</objectId>
                <parent>llcCcOperEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>Integer32</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-write</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object denotes the maximum I PDU size, in&lt;br&gt;octets, that this LLC SAP may send to its&lt;br&gt;remote connection component partner. This count&lt;br&gt;is referred to as 'N1' in the IEEE 802.2&lt;br&gt;specification [??].&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;At connection setup, the remote LLC may send,&lt;br&gt;using an XID frame, the maximum I PDU size&lt;br&gt;which it is prepared to receive. If so, an&lt;br&gt;implementation may choose to override the&lt;br&gt;administered maximum PDU size with the&lt;br&gt;dynamically learned value and should reflect&lt;br&gt;that in this object.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The I PDU size includes all octets in a frame,&lt;br&gt;excluding framing characters, the MAC header&lt;br&gt;and link link header.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcCcOperMaxIPDUOctetsRcv</objectName>
                <objectId>4</objectId>
                <parent>llcCcOperEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>Integer32</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-write</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object denotes the maximum I PDU size,in&lt;br&gt;octets, that this LLC can expect to receive&lt;br&gt;from its remote LLC partner. This count is&lt;br&gt;referred to as 'N1' in the IEEE 802.2&lt;br&gt;specification [??]&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The I PDU size includes all octets in a frame&lt;br&gt;with the exception of the framing characters,&lt;br&gt;the MAC header and the link header.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcCcOperMaxUnackedIPDUsSend</objectName>
                <objectId>5</objectId>
                <parent>llcCcOperEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>INTEGER(1..127)</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-write</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object denotes the maximum consequetive&lt;br&gt;unacknowledged I PDU frames that this LLC may&lt;br&gt;send to its remote LLC partner. This count is&lt;br&gt;referred to as 'k' in the IEEE 802.2&lt;br&gt;specification [??].&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;At connection setup, the remote LLC may send,&lt;br&gt;using an XID frame, the maximum number of&lt;br&gt;unacknowledged I PDUs which it is prepared to&lt;br&gt;receive. If so, an implementation may choose to&lt;br&gt;override the administered maximum number of&lt;br&gt;unacknowledged PDUs with the dynamicly learned&lt;br&gt;value and should reflect that in this object.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcCcOperMaxUnackedIPDUsRcv</objectName>
                <objectId>6</objectId>
                <parent>llcCcOperEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>INTEGER(1..127)</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-write</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object denotes the maximum number of&lt;br&gt;unacknowledged I PDUs that this LLC can expect&lt;br&gt;to receive from its remote LLC partner. This&lt;br&gt;count is referred to as 'k' in the IEEE 802.2&lt;br&gt;specification [??].</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcCcOperMaxRetransmits</objectName>
                <objectId>7</objectId>
                <parent>llcCcOperEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>INTEGER</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-write</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object denotes the value for the maximum&lt;br&gt;number of times that this LLC shall retry PDUs&lt;br&gt;following the expiration of the acknowledgement&lt;br&gt;timer, the P-bit timer or the reject timer.&lt;br&gt;When these retries are exhausted, the link&lt;br&gt;shall be declared inactive.  This count is&lt;br&gt;referred to as 'N2' in the IEEE 802.2&lt;br&gt;specification [??].</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcCcOperAckTimer</objectName>
                <objectId>8</objectId>
                <parent>llcCcOperEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>TimeTicks</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-write</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object denotes the value for the time&lt;br&gt;interval during which this LLC shall expect to&lt;br&gt;receive either:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1) an acknowledgement to one or more&lt;br&gt;outstanding I PDUs.  or 2) a response PDU to an&lt;br&gt;unnumbered command PDU.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The expiration of this timer shall cause the&lt;br&gt;frame unacknowledged frames to be retransmitted&lt;br&gt;(up to N2 times).</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcCcOperPbitTimer</objectName>
                <objectId>9</objectId>
                <parent>llcCcOperEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>TimeTicks</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-write</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object denotes the value for the time&lt;br&gt;interval during which this LLC shall expect to&lt;br&gt;receive a PDU with the F bit set to '1' in&lt;br&gt;response to a Type 2 command with the P bit set&lt;br&gt;to '1'.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The expiration of this timer shall cause the&lt;br&gt;REJ PDU to be retransmitted (up to N2 times).</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcCcOperRejTimer</objectName>
                <objectId>10</objectId>
                <parent>llcCcOperEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>TimeTicks</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-write</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object denotes the value for the time&lt;br&gt;interval during which this LLC shall expect to&lt;br&gt;receive a reply to a REJ PDU.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The expiration of this timer shall cause the&lt;br&gt;REJ PDU to be retransmitted (up to N2 times).</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcCcOperBusyTimer</objectName>
                <objectId>11</objectId>
                <parent>llcCcOperEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>TimeTicks</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-write</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object denotes the value for the time&lt;br&gt;interval during which this LLC shall expect to&lt;br&gt;receive an indication that a busy condition at&lt;br&gt;the remote LLC has cleared.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The expiration of this timer shall cause the&lt;br&gt;link to be declared inactive.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcCcOperInactTimer</objectName>
                <objectId>12</objectId>
                <parent>llcCcOperEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>TimeTicks</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-write</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object denotes the value for the time&lt;br&gt;interval during which this LLC shall expect to&lt;br&gt;receive any PDU from the remote LLC.  This&lt;br&gt;function is not described in the IEEE 802.2&lt;br&gt;specification [??] but is widely implemented.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The expiration of this timer shall cause the&lt;br&gt;local LLC to send a PDU to the remote LLC with&lt;br&gt;the P bit set to '1'.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Any value for this object less than or equal to&lt;br&gt;the acknowledgement timer shall mean that the&lt;br&gt;timer is not used.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcCcOperDelayAckCount</objectName>
                <objectId>13</objectId>
                <parent>llcCcOperEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>INTEGER</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-write</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object denotes the value for the maximum&lt;br&gt;number of consequetive I PDUs which this LLC&lt;br&gt;shall receive during the interval defined by&lt;br&gt;llcCcOperDelayTimer without sending an&lt;br&gt;immediate acknowledgement.  This must be less&lt;br&gt;than or equal to the value of&lt;br&gt;llcCcOperMaxUnackIPDURcv. This function is not&lt;br&gt;described in the IEEE 802.2 specification [??]&lt;br&gt;but is widely implemented.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A value of one indicates that acknowledgments&lt;br&gt;will be sent immediately and that the value of&lt;br&gt;llcCcOperDelayAckTimer should be ignored.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcCcOperDelayAckTimer</objectName>
                <objectId>14</objectId>
                <parent>llcCcOperEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>TimeTicks</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-write</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object denotes the value for the time&lt;br&gt;interval during which this LLC shall delay&lt;br&gt;acknowledgment of one or more I PDUs (up to the&lt;br&gt;value of llcCcOperDelayAckCount). This function&lt;br&gt;is not described in the IEEE 802.2&lt;br&gt;specification [??] but is widely implemented.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The expiration of this timer shall cause the&lt;br&gt;local LLC to acknowledge all unacknowledged I&lt;br&gt;PDUs.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This object is associated with the&lt;br&gt;llcCcOperDelayAckCount object and only has&lt;br&gt;meaning if that object has a value greater than&lt;br&gt;one.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcCcOperCreateTime</objectName>
                <objectId>15</objectId>
                <parent>llcCcOperEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>TimeTicks</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-only</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object describes the value of sysUpTime&lt;br&gt;when this connection was created.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcCcOperLastModifyTime</objectName>
                <objectId>16</objectId>
                <parent>llcCcOperEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>TimeTicks</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-only</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object describes the value of sysUpTime&lt;br&gt;when this connection definition was last&lt;br&gt;modified.  If the connection has not been&lt;br&gt;modified, then this value shall be zero.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcCcOperLastFailTime</objectName>
                <objectId>17</objectId>
                <parent>llcCcOperEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>TimeTicks</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-only</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object describes the value of sysUpTime&lt;br&gt;when this LLC link station last failed.  If&lt;br&gt;the link station has not failed, then this&lt;br&gt;value shall be zero.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcCcOperLastFailCause</objectName>
                <objectId>18</objectId>
                <parent>llcCcOperEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>INTEGER</type>
                    <valueList>
                        <valueItem>
                            <label>undefined</label>
                            <val>1</val>
                        </valueItem>
                        <valueItem>
                            <label>rxFRMR</label>
                            <val>2</val>
                        </valueItem>
                        <valueItem>
                            <label>txFRMR</label>
                            <val>3</val>
                        </valueItem>
                        <valueItem>
                            <label>noResponse</label>
                            <val>4</val>
                        </valueItem>
                        <valueItem>
                            <label>protocolErr</label>
                            <val>5</val>
                        </valueItem>
                        <valueItem>
                            <label>noActivity</label>
                            <val>6</val>
                        </valueItem>
                        <valueItem>
                            <label>discReceived</label>
                            <val>7</val>
                        </valueItem>
                        <valueItem>
                            <label>dmReceived</label>
                            <val>8</val>
                        </valueItem>
                        <valueItem>
                            <label>retriesExpired</label>
                            <val>9</val>
                        </valueItem>
                    </valueList>
                    <defaultValue>undefined</defaultValue>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-only</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This enumerated object reflects the cause of the&lt;br&gt;last failure of this LLC link station.  If the link&lt;br&gt;station has not failed, then this object will have&lt;br&gt;a value of undefined(1).</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcCcOperLastFailFRMRInfo</objectName>
                <objectId>19</objectId>
                <parent>llcCcOperEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>OCTET STRING(SIZE(3))</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-only</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object reflects the information field of the&lt;br&gt;FRMR frame if the last failure for this LLC link&lt;br&gt;station was as a result of an invalid frame.&lt;br&gt;Otherwise, this field has no meaning.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcCcStatsTable</objectName>
                <objectId>3</objectId>
                <parent>llcCcGroup</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <sequence>LlcCcStatsEntry</sequence>
                </syntax>
                <access>not-accessible</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>Each entry in this table contains statistics&lt;br&gt;for a specific LLC link station.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcCcStatsEntry</objectName>
                <objectId>1</objectId>
                <parent>llcCcStatsTable</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>LlcCcStatsEntry</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>not-accessible</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>A list of statistics for an LLC link station.</description>
                <indices>
                    <index>ifIndex</index>
                    <index>llcCcLSap</index>
                    <index>llcCcRSap</index>
                    <index>llcCcRMac</index>
                    <index>llcCcLMac</index>
                </indices>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcCcStatsLocalBusies</objectName>
                <objectId>1</objectId>
                <parent>llcCcStatsEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>Counter32</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-only</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object reflects the total number of times&lt;br&gt;that the local LLC link station has entered a&lt;br&gt;busy state (RNR) since link station startup.&lt;br&gt;At link station startup time, this object must&lt;br&gt;be initialized to zero.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcCcStatsRemoteBusies</objectName>
                <objectId>2</objectId>
                <parent>llcCcStatsEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>Counter32</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-only</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object reflects the total number of times&lt;br&gt;that an adjacent ( remote) LLC link station&lt;br&gt;has entered a busy state (RNR) since link&lt;br&gt;station startup.  At link station startup time,&lt;br&gt;this object must be initialized to zero.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcCcStatsIFramesIn</objectName>
                <objectId>3</objectId>
                <parent>llcCcStatsEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>Counter32</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-only</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object reflects the total I-frames&lt;br&gt;received from an adjacent LLC link station&lt;br&gt;since link station startup.  At link station&lt;br&gt;startup time, this object must be initialized&lt;br&gt;to zero.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcCcStatsIFramesOut</objectName>
                <objectId>4</objectId>
                <parent>llcCcStatsEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>Counter32</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-only</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object reflects the total I-frames&lt;br&gt;transmitted to an adjacent LLC link station&lt;br&gt;since link station startup.  At link station&lt;br&gt;startup time, this object must be initialized&lt;br&gt;to zero.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcCcStatsIOctetsIn</objectName>
                <objectId>5</objectId>
                <parent>llcCcStatsEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>Counter32</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-only</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object reflects the total octets&lt;br&gt;contained in I-frames received from an adjacent&lt;br&gt;LLC link station since link station startup.&lt;br&gt;At link station startup time, this object must&lt;br&gt;be initialized to zero.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcCcStatsIOctetsOut</objectName>
                <objectId>6</objectId>
                <parent>llcCcStatsEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>Counter32</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-only</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object reflects the total octets&lt;br&gt;contained in I-frames transmitted to an&lt;br&gt;adjacent LLC link station since link station&lt;br&gt;startup.  At link station startup time,&lt;br&gt;this object must be initialized to zero.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcCcStatsREJsIn</objectName>
                <objectId>7</objectId>
                <parent>llcCcStatsEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>Counter32</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-only</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object reflects the total REJ frames&lt;br&gt;received from an adjacent LLC link station&lt;br&gt;since link station startup.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcCcStatsREJsOut</objectName>
                <objectId>8</objectId>
                <parent>llcCcStatsEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>Counter32</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-only</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object reflects the total REJ frames&lt;br&gt;transmitted to an adjacent LLC link station&lt;br&gt;since link station startup.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcCcStatsRetransmitsIn</objectName>
                <objectId>9</objectId>
                <parent>llcCcStatsEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>Counter32</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-only</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object reflects the total number of information&lt;br&gt;frames retransmitted by the remote link station&lt;br&gt;because the N(s) received from that link station&lt;br&gt;indicated that one or more information frames&lt;br&gt;sent by that station were lost.  This event&lt;br&gt;causes the first missing information frame of a&lt;br&gt;window and all subsequent information frames to&lt;br&gt;be retransmitted.  At link station startup time,&lt;br&gt;this object must be initialized to zero</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcCcStatsRetransmitsOut</objectName>
                <objectId>10</objectId>
                <parent>llcCcStatsEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>Counter32</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-only</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object reflects the total number of&lt;br&gt;information frames retransmitted to a remote&lt;br&gt;link station because the N(r) received from&lt;br&gt;that link station indicated that one or more&lt;br&gt;information frames sent to that station were&lt;br&gt;lost. This event causes the first missing&lt;br&gt;information frame of a window and all&lt;br&gt;subsequent information frames to be&lt;br&gt;retransmitted.  At link station startup time,&lt;br&gt;this object must be initialized to zero.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcCcStatsFRMRsIn</objectName>
                <objectId>11</objectId>
                <parent>llcCcStatsEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>Counter32</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-only</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object reflects the total frame reject&lt;br&gt;(FRMR) frames received from an adjacent LLC&lt;br&gt;link station since link station startup.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcCcStatsFRMRsOut</objectName>
                <objectId>12</objectId>
                <parent>llcCcStatsEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>Counter32</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-only</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object reflects the total frame reject&lt;br&gt;(FRMR) frames transmitted to an adjacent LLC&lt;br&gt;link station since link station startup.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcCcStatsDISCsIn</objectName>
                <objectId>13</objectId>
                <parent>llcCcStatsEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>Counter32</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-only</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object reflects the total number of&lt;br&gt;disconnect (DISC) requests received from an&lt;br&gt;adjacent link station since link station&lt;br&gt;startup.  At link station startup time, this&lt;br&gt;object must be initialized to zero.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcCcStatsDISCsOut</objectName>
                <objectId>14</objectId>
                <parent>llcCcStatsEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>Counter32</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-only</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object reflects the total number of&lt;br&gt;disconnect (DISC) requests transmited to an&lt;br&gt;adjacent link station since link station&lt;br&gt;startup.  At link station startup time, this&lt;br&gt;object must be initialized to zero.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcCcStatsUAsIn</objectName>
                <objectId>15</objectId>
                <parent>llcCcStatsEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>Counter32</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-only</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object reflects the total number of&lt;br&gt;unnumbered acknowledgements (UA) requests&lt;br&gt;received from an adjacent link station&lt;br&gt;since link station startup.  At link station&lt;br&gt;startup time, this object must be initialized&lt;br&gt;to zero.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcCcStatsUAsOut</objectName>
                <objectId>16</objectId>
                <parent>llcCcStatsEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>Counter32</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-only</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object reflects the total number of&lt;br&gt;unnumbered acknowledgements (UA) requests&lt;br&gt;transmited to an adjacent link station&lt;br&gt;since link station startup.  At link station&lt;br&gt;startup time, this object must be initialized&lt;br&gt;to zero.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcCcStatsDMsIn</objectName>
                <objectId>17</objectId>
                <parent>llcCcStatsEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>Counter32</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-only</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object reflects the total number of&lt;br&gt;disconnect mode (DM) requests received from an&lt;br&gt;adjacent link station since link station&lt;br&gt;startup.  At link station startup time, this&lt;br&gt;object must be initialized to zero.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcCcStatsDMsOut</objectName>
                <objectId>18</objectId>
                <parent>llcCcStatsEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>Counter32</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-only</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object reflects the total number of&lt;br&gt;disconnect mode (DM) requests transmited to an&lt;br&gt;adjacent link station since link station&lt;br&gt;startup.  At link station startup time, this&lt;br&gt;object must be initialized to zero.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcCcStatsSABMEsIn</objectName>
                <objectId>19</objectId>
                <parent>llcCcStatsEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>Counter32</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-only</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object reflects the total number of&lt;br&gt;set normal response mode (SABME) requests&lt;br&gt;received from an adjacent link station&lt;br&gt;since link station startup.  At link station&lt;br&gt;startup time, this object must be initialized&lt;br&gt;to zero.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcCcStatsSABMEsOut</objectName>
                <objectId>20</objectId>
                <parent>llcCcStatsEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>Counter32</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-only</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object reflects the total number of&lt;br&gt;set normal response mode (SABME) requests&lt;br&gt;transmited to an adjacent link station&lt;br&gt;since link station startup.  At link station&lt;br&gt;startup time, this object must be initialized&lt;br&gt;to zero.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcCcStatsProtocolErrs</objectName>
                <objectId>21</objectId>
                <parent>llcCcStatsEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>Counter32</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-only</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object reflects the total occurrences,&lt;br&gt;since link station startup, where this LLC&lt;br&gt;link station has inactivated the link as a&lt;br&gt;result of receiving a frame from its adjacent&lt;br&gt;link station which was in violation of the&lt;br&gt;protocol.  At link station startup time, this&lt;br&gt;object must be initialized to zero.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcCcStatsActivityTOs</objectName>
                <objectId>22</objectId>
                <parent>llcCcStatsEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>Counter32</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-only</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object reflects the total occurrences,&lt;br&gt;since startup, where this LLC link station has&lt;br&gt;inactivated the link as a result of no activity&lt;br&gt;on the link.  At link station startup time,&lt;br&gt;this object must be initialized to zero.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectType>
                <objectName>llcCcStatsRetriesExps</objectName>
                <objectId>23</objectId>
                <parent>llcCcStatsEntry</parent>
                <syntax>
                    <type>Counter32</type>
                </syntax>
                <access>read-only</access>
                <status>mandatory</status>
                <description>This object reflects the total occurrences,&lt;br&gt;since startup, where this LLC link station has&lt;br&gt;inactivated the link as a result of a retry&lt;br&gt;sequence being exhausted.  At link station&lt;br&gt;startup time, this object must be initialized&lt;br&gt;to zero.</description>
            </objectType>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectIdentifier>
                <objectName>llcCorePortAdminGroup</objectName>
                <objectId>1</objectId>
                <parent>llcCoreGroups</parent>
            </objectIdentifier>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectIdentifier>
                <objectName>llcCorePortOperGroup</objectName>
                <objectId>2</objectId>
                <parent>llcCoreGroups</parent>
            </objectIdentifier>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectIdentifier>
                <objectName>llcCorePortStatsGroup</objectName>
                <objectId>3</objectId>
                <parent>llcCoreGroups</parent>
            </objectIdentifier>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectIdentifier>
                <objectName>llcCoreCcAdminGroup</objectName>
                <objectId>4</objectId>
                <parent>llcCoreGroups</parent>
            </objectIdentifier>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectIdentifier>
                <objectName>llcCoreCcOperGroup</objectName>
                <objectId>5</objectId>
                <parent>llcCoreGroups</parent>
            </objectIdentifier>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectIdentifier>
                <objectName>llcCoreCcStatsGroup</objectName>
                <objectId>6</objectId>
                <parent>llcCoreGroups</parent>
            </objectIdentifier>
        </mibObject>
        <mibObject>
            <objectIdentifier>
                <objectName>llcCoreCompliance</objectName>
                <objectId>1</objectId>
                <parent>llcCompliances</parent>
            </objectIdentifier>
        </mibObject>
    </objects>
</mib>
